Toggle navigation [**MUDFISH**](https://mudfish.net/)

    * Main Products
    
    * Other Products

    * List
    * Document
    
    * Status
    
    * Tools

Privacy Policy (Effective Date: January 19, 2016)
=================================================

General
-------

Mudfish Networks and its affiliates (hereinafter, "we", "us" or "our") are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This Privacy Policy (together with our Terms and Conditions of Use) governs our collection, processing and use of your Personal Information. We define "Personal Information" as information which identifies you personally, e.g. your name, address and e-mail address etc.

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you of:

1. the kinds of Personal Information which we may collect about you and how it may be used;
2. our use of information regarding IP Addresses and our use of cookies;
3. any disclosure of Personal Information to third parties;
4. your ability to correct, update and delete your Personal Information; and
5. the security measures we have in place to prevent the loss, misuse, or alteration of Personal Information under our control.

Anonymity
---------

While we always anonymize your true IP address while using the Services, remember that no VPN provider can control what other apps collect from your device or what cookies other websites or third parties place in your browser.

* Our product will never store, log, or share your true IP address, and we always delete your true IP address after your VPN session is closed.
* We never associate your email, true IP address, username, or unique mobile ID with your browsing information or online activities when you are using Mudfish.
* We never share your personal information with unaffiliated third parties other than service providers that we use for internal technology and business operations (such as website hosting, payment processing, data analysis, information technology, customer service, and email delivery).
* We only use your information to provide you with amazing products and services that we are constantly working to improve.

Automatically Collected Information
-----------------------------------

When you use our Services, we collect information about you or your device automatically. Here's a fuller explanation of the types of information we collect when you use our Services:

* When you visit our websites:
    * We and our third party service providers may automatically collect information from your device, sometimes by placing cookies, beacons, and similar technologies in your browser and on emails that we send you. We may use this information, for example, to ensure that the Services function properly, to determine how many users have visited certain pages or opened messages or newsletters, or to prevent fraud. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to automatically decline cookies or be given the choice of declining or accepting the transfer to your computer of a particular cookie (or cookies) from a particular site. You may also wish to refer to [http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/index.html](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/index.html). Keep in mind though, if you do not accept cookies, you may experience some inconvenience in your use of the Services.
    * Your IP address may be collected when you visit our websites. Collecting IP addresses is standard practice and is done automatically by many websites and other online services. We use IP addresses for internal purposes such as calculating usage levels and diagnosing server problems. We may also use your IP address to derive your approximate location. Downloading and turning on Mudfish will make your true IP address private to our websites, as well as websites of third parties. Using our websites or other websites without turning on Mudfish may allow your IP address to be collected.
    * We collect device-specific information, such as the hardware model, operating system version, browser type, language, wireless network, and mobile network information. This information does not identify you, and we use it to provide and improve the Services, troubleshoot, and perform analytics.
* When you launch Mudfish:
    * We collect your IP address, immediately obfuscate and anonymize it, and provide you with a virtual or proxy IP address. We may also use your IP address to derive your approximate location in order to effectively provide the Services. Again, your true IP address is stored only for the duration of your VPN session and is cleared after your session is closed. We do not associate your true IP address with your online activities and we do not store or log your true IP address after the end of your session.
    * When you launch Mudfish, we also collect device-specific information, such as the hardware model, operating system version, browser type, language, wireless network, and mobile network information. This information does not identify you, and we use it to provide and improve the Services, troubleshoot, and perform analytics on our services.
    * When you use Mudfish to access the internet, we collect only anonymous, aggregate data about which websites you visit and which apps you use. We do not attribute any specific website visits or app usage to any specific user. We collect this information to:
        1. Perform analytics on our services, including measuring whether our users are able to successfully access certain websites or apps;
        2. Troubleshoot service issues and improve service quality;
        3. Place generic ads in front of specific apps or websites.

International Cross-Border Data Transfer
----------------------------------------

Mudfish uses servers hosted in the South Korea. Please note that we may be transferring your information outside of your region for storage and processing in the South Korea and around the globe. By using the Services you consent to the transfer of information to countries outside of your country of residence, including the South Korea, which may have data protection rules that are different from those of your country.

Cookies
-------

We use a browser feature known as a "cookie", which assigns a unique identification to your computer. Cookies are typically stored on your computer's hard drive. Information collected from cookies is used by us to evaluate the effectiveness of our Site, analyse trends, and administer the Mudfish service. The information collected from cookies allows us to determine such things as which parts of our Site are most visited and difficulties our visitors may experience in accessing our Site. With this knowledge, we can improve the quality of your experience on the Mudfish server by recognising and delivering more of the most desired features and information, as well as by resolving access difficulties. We also use cookies and/or a technology known as web bugs or clear gifs, which are typically stored in emails to help us confirm your receipt of, and response to, our emails and to provide you with a more personalised experience when using our Site.

We use third party service provider(s), to assist us in better understanding the use of our Site. Our service provider(s) will place cookies on the hard drive of your computer and will receive information that we select that will educate us on such things as how visitors navigate around our site, what products are browsed. Our service provider(s) analyses this information and provides us with aggregate reports. The information and analysis provided by our service provider(s) will be used to assist us in better understanding our visitors' interests in our Site and how to better serve those interests. The information collected by our service provider(s) may be linked to and combined with information that we collect about you while you are using the Mudfish service. Our service provider(s) is/are contractually restricted from using information they receive from our Site other than to assist us.

By using our Site you are agreeing that we may use cookies for the purposes set out above.

Marketing
---------

Mudfish Networks don't use or sell your Personal Information for marketing purposes. You'll get explicitly E-Mail from Mudfish Networks for your agreement when Mudfish Networks wants to use your Personal Information for marketing purposes.

Changes
-------

Our Site policies, content, information, promotions, disclosures, disclaimers and features may be revised, modified, updated, and/or supplemented at any time and without prior notice at the sole and absolute discretion of Mudfish Networks. If we change this Privacy Policy, will take steps to notify all users by a notice on our Site and will post the amended Privacy Policy on the Site.

Contact Us
----------

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy and/or practices as it or they relate to the Mudfish service, please contact us at the following e-mail address, address and telephone number:

E-Mail: support@loxch.com

##### MUDFISH

[Terms Of Service](https://mudfish.net/agreement/tos "Term Of Service") [Privacy Policy](https://mudfish.net/agreement/privacy_policy "Privacy Policy") [Refund Policy](https://docs.mudfish.net/en/docs/mudfish-policy/refund-policy/ "Refund Policy") [Language](javascript:void(0); "Language")

##### Mudfish Networks

[Contact Us](javascript:void();) [We're hiring!](https://mudfish.net/hire)

##### Miscellaneous

© 2011-2024 Mudfish Networks Inc.
